AKSHAY GORE

420 Nord Avenue, Apt. #5, Chico, CA, 95926

Contact: 408-921-5838| Email : akshaygore06@gmail.com LinkedIn : https://www.linkedin.com/in/akshaygore

GitHub: https://github.com/akshaygore06/ Portfolio: https://github.com/akshaygore06/

Summary

Worked as database management intern at Distributed Learning Technologies, CSU Chico. Have two years of work experience as a software engineer. Strong logical and analytical skills. Seeking internship/full time opportunity in the field of Software or Web Development.

Education

• MS in Computer Science, California State University – Chico, CA (Aug 2014 – Dec 2016) GPA 3.7/4.0

BE in Computer Technology, University of Nagpur, India (Aug 2008 – Dec 2012):

GPA 3.5/4.0

Work experience

Intern, Distributed Learning Technologies, CSU Chico, CA

Jan 2016 - May 2016

- Designed a SITE USAGE report generation system for Blackboard LEARN website.
- Created complex queries using multiple select and joins queries to generate the reports.
- Worked on the Google Analytics and Microsoft PowerBI to analyze the traffic.

Software Engineer, Inboxmasters Systems Pvt. Ltd. - Pune, India

Dec 2012 - May 2014

- Responsibilities included design and development of Email Marketing Campaign, Requirement Analysis, data monitoring and tracking.
- Designed and developed data queries to target the specific users and provide efficient email marketing campaign for clients.
- Prepared data analysis listings and activity, performance and progress reports.

Academic Projects

Mozilla Open Source Project

- Resolved many core and documentation bugs in different languages like CPP and Java script.
- Performed unit, regression and integration testing on different products of Mozilla Community.

Book Tracking System

 Developed an online system for the Office of Accessible Technology and Services which manages alternative media transactions for disabled students.

Gold Chase

- Developed a real time multiplayer game in C++ on Unix system.
- Independently developed code incorporating shared memory, semaphores and graphics rendering.

Library Search Engine

• Developed a Search Engine to search for all possible results from given library database.

Skills & Expertise

Languages: C++, SQL, PL/SQL, Java, Python, Java Script, HTML, CSS, Android Development, JSP

Technical expertise: Google Test, RDBMS, Oracle SQL Data Modeler, GIT, Bootstrap, Eclipse IDE, Visual Studio, Amazon Web Services, Linux, Windows, Mac, Android Studio, Algorithms, Oracle XE Database, GDB, VIM

Courses

Software Engineering | Distributed Systems | Advance Database Mgmt. Systems | Object-Oriented Programming | Algorithm and Data Structures | Mobile Application Development | Design and Analysis of Algorithms

